

GRADEN GRANDISON

graden.s.grandison@gmail.com | 1+ (519) 806-4747 | Mono, ON L9W 6H9

Summary

Dedicated individual with a proven history of leadership and passion for serving others. Committed to devoting resources and energy towards providing campers with a memorable experience, allowing them to thrive spiritually in a warm, welcoming and safe environment. Excellent interpersonal, multitasking and prioritization skills.

Skills

- Strong Interpersonal skills
- Leadership
- Active listening

- Training & Development
- Social and religious assistance
- Troubleshooting

Experience

Summer Camp Coordinator

07/2021 - 08/2021

- Broadway Pentecostal Church | Mono, ON Created and oversaw implementation of schedules and procedures for entire camp operations comprising 10+ volunteers and 40+ campers.
 - Supervised material acquisition, setup and teardown for special events.
 - Initiated creative ideas and kept recreation programs entertaining and refreshing.

Power 2 Change Guelph | Guelph, ON **Active Member**

09/2020 - Current

• Developed new member relationships through community event attendance and involvement

 Deepened and retained member relationships through intentional communication and engagement of participants

VIDA | San Jose, Costa Rica Medical Volunteer 04/2022 - 05/2022

- Volunteered in rural villages around Costa Rica providing medical support to local men, women and children of all ages.
- Collaborated with healthcare teams to determine needs and support daily objectives.
- Gathered and documented vital signs such as temperature, pulse and respiration.

Faith Fellowship | Mono, ON **Church Volunteer**

01/2013 - Current

- Delivered food and clothing to struggling members of the community unable to get to food bank
- Demonstrated and reinforced values of caring, respect, honesty and responsibility
- Planned and implemented appropriate program activities for children and adults

Alpha | Guelph, ON **Table Host** 10/2020 - 03/2021

- Supported small group discussions with attendees
- Supervised activities with the aim of maintaining the comfort levels and support of guests
- Collaborated with colleagues to address questions of participants

Ontario Pioneer Summer Camp | Port Sydney, ON

Impact Crew Member

08/2017 - 08/2019

- Camp Facility maintenance and supervision of common areas
- Mentorship of younger campers
- Upheld high standards of productivity and quality in all areas of operations

Faith Fellowship Pentecostal Church | Mono, ON

Vacation Bible School Student Leader 07/2017 - 08/2019

- Supervised attendees and volunteers ensuring access to a safe and non-threatening space for learning and worship.
- Assisted with daily camp functions, including learning centers, crafts, snacks, memory verse work, student manual completion, passing out stickers and reading the Bible.
- Planned and led children in activities and structured game times, prayer, storytelling and creative Bible teaching.

Education and Training

University of Guelph | Guelph, ON **Bachelor of Science** in Biomedical Sciences *Expected in 04/2024*

Accomplishments

- Graduating Class Salutatorian (2020) Robert F. Hall
- Honor Roll [Grade 9 Grade 12]
- Hall Hero (awarded for strong work ethic during COVID-19)
- ROPSSA Football Champions (2019)
- Top French Award [Grade 12]
- Dean's Honor List University of Guelph (2020/22)

Additional Information

• References available upon request